lee yon e
kim yong gwan
and also Park Yoon Woo
poton camuldu
all names and matches are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
you're really going to quit
after this case
to be honest
here you get more
than in a year in that company
and if you quit this business
Do you want to earn money like this for the rest of your life?
but we can leave
when we earn a little more
and how much is 1000000000 2 1000000000
you know
money is not the main thing
happy street house 50
Looks like he has a speech disorder
transfer him to the general ward and observe
and contact the guardian
he needs his head well
hwangjo hyung now we
where did he go
hwangjeong hyung
jong hyun
are you here
episode 10
we don't have any cameras anymore
it must be hard for him to move
and he's still in shock
where did he go
immediately after waking up he could head
they have an unusually strong bond for regular junkies
I thought he would avenge his brother
and he fell into someone
instead of an incident, a telephone booth in the haenbok area
really
to kanensu's house
partner
the subscriber cannot answer your call now
please leave a message after
let's talk
I'm near your house
I'll wait until you come out
I need
who are you
I'd rather work in a club
or a nanny for a rich family
I heard you work as a housekeeper for a teacher sua it’s true
art teacher
you do this together
Kopen street 12
mom
you have 2 phones
here
doesn't look like 9 kilos
I'll give you the rest when you pay
do you think chebolino carries with him 2 1000000000 in cash
oh, watch enough of your dramas
then the deal is cancelled, so stand by
and how did you become partners?
both are so impatient
or is it in the past
the subscriber cannot answer your call now
please leave a message after the signal
but here it is, I thought you were experienced
This is the first time you've seen such a sum
now my condition
james information about him
his real name
and why the hell did he stick to me
It's not in my best interest to get involved in a bad deal
if you tell me everything
I will take good care of your money and your safety
as easy as shelling pears
I'll explain everything hand in hand
let me tell you
why did I do this
his real name
listen to me
yes
this is weird
I know my wife insu
you're not like that
because of you she became like this
stop and listen
all because of your treatment and your debt
don't pretend you don't understand
it's because of you
she became like this
do you think she suddenly wanted to get rich?
your wife wanted to completely end it from the very beginning
as soon as your debts are paid off
so just give it to me
I will make sure that your family
there were no more problems
you
you're selling them
I'm calling the police oh you want
to tie her up sua
dad help me
some kind of person
kidnapped and tied me up
dad
please save me
dad I'm very scared
I beg you to help
sua a papa
dad what's wrong with you
how are you
아하
아아
please don't
hey shinchang wake up
no, please, I beg you
why are you doing this to me why
leave quickly
teacher
sua are you okay?
when meeting in Medusa, he introduced himself as James
I don't know my real name
if I were a patka
Yes, I could come up with something for money
but I don't want to lie
what if I fulfilled my part of the deal?
they'll only take this
jokes jokes
ah
let me kill you want to
I'm an honest person
exchanged goods for money
what kind of relationship
damn
unless you're going to torture me
then don't tie up the sucker
Sorry, but you left the recorder on
yes of course as you asked
nothing happened thanks
we can go fast yeah yeah
missed daughter
mama save me
으아
으아으아
sua sua
run away quickly
으아
으악으악
으악
right
right rib
broken ribs on the right
Apparently they haven't grown together yet
su
sua what happened
what's wrong with the hand
where are you from?
here they are, here you go
hey hey hey stop thug
calm down let's take him away
here's a rowdy one
everything is fine don't be afraid he left
apparently he knows you insu
2 hours earlier
I've already written this vegetable off
you'll get bored of gyeongdong
you can't be stubborn
even though you're pretty bad in other ways
I remember you once told me
The main thing for the police is persistence
what happened why
how did you get to this point
everyone wants to live well
but not everyone can do it
in our world
that's how I became
so mind your own business
keep up the good work
there's nothing left for me
except to get into your 7
you failed to protect the fetus in the womb
but you can protect a living child
I agree kendo
I was very scared
there are some injuries
no
you taught with the victim right
yes
have you previously dated your attacker?
it means you don’t know why you attacked
How did you find the victim?
teacher, how did you find out where the girl is?
damn
I'm outside happy
55 people unconscious
he is a cancer patient
come soon
Sua shared her location
I went on foot because of the snowfall
and heard a scream from the house
where do you live
you live far away
what are you
did it on the spot
where were you kidnapped
please answer
what do you do
my daughter is injured
this was found in her bag
the suspect took the substance from here
and tried to introduce it to your daughter
did you know what's in this package?
no
how did you get them?
why did you take them home
promised to pay
who
who got this one involved
baby like this
I don't know
a post was published in the app
I wrote in a personal message
and they told me the place
Apparently you still don't understand
what did you do
you distributed drugs
you know how serious this is
I
I'm not
wait let's go out
we can talk together
detective kim yes yes
take her to the interrogation room
follow me
I'll be there soon
you can go
is it a teacher and we're done
you are free if you have any questions
I'll contact you okay
decide who you are for
if you don't want to rattle
James
what a shame
my daughter wouldn't do that, you set her up
you don't know her well
did you really assign a man to her?
and you wanted me to stay
without safety net
imagine my surprise
1 time I see a mother giving drugs to her daughter
this is
was not me I promise this is the last time
I thought so too
I'll stop here
just 1 time and more
then I'll definitely leave
right
I perfectly understand people like you
I was told that I could earn money
my family doesn't know
I felt the same way then
you know
maybe we're even similar
you're constantly holding something back inside of you
exactly like me before
but such things are necessary
will come out
outward
according to my experience
you will do everything you say
then bring me everything
everything there is
I want to kill them all
let's go jenhee
everyone who touches my daughter
and 7 Jenha's mom
that's not possible
everyone who despises us
where did you go
I want
so they can't hurt us anymore
oh my god mom sua
get it
take a bite
you really wanted to end everything
for example, if you want more free space
you can
sit down don't be shy
beauty
then
let's trade I agree
only together
the police are always kind to citizens
hey kyondo
are you okay
detective what
captain chan lent you a loan
Well, there were a couple of times when they suspended me
I tried to give him everything back
but he didn't take it
be careful
so as not to end up like me
her kenda
하
let me tell you
what happens next
your daughter will go to prison
husband will die after a course of cheap chemotherapy
and all because I will inform the tax office about your income
will leave you without a livelihood
and you will lose your home
you can try to go somewhere with your daughter
far away
what the hell is not joking
but I will look for you
and I will definitely find it
and then
I will destroy everyone
everyone you love
everyone you try so hard to protect
in this
me
no
equal
what do you want
speak
listen
you can call me
if you have anything to tell
or need help
I don't think this is the end yet
wait
taxi
why don't they stop right there?
I didn't know
everything seemed strange
but I didn't know
I'm telling the honest truth
me
just needed money
what do you need money for studying?
I want to go to art school
this requires money
you already spend a lot on your dad’s treatment
so I decided
mom
what will happen now
I'm going to jail
mom I don't want to go to jail
mommy no
they won't put you in jail no one will put you in jail
trust me don't worry
mommy forgive me
please forgive me
I really didn't want to
I asked him to tell you everything
but apparently he didn’t, the tumor began to grow again
in addition to the background of an immunodeficiency state
he got an infection and
resulting in septic shock
for now let's start with a course of antibiotics
but even if he comes to his senses
The prognosis for cancer is still unfavorable
and what should I do
options
in the treatment of pancreatic ductal adenocorcinoma
treatment with heavy ions also gives good results
however, it is not yet carried out in Korea
but given your husband’s current condition, the flight is contraindicated
mom mom
don't go funeral home mom
mommy no
how come mom
but last week I noticed some scuff marks
insu you are great
that everything works out for me
if only
that bag didn't arrive
to our house
if I had reported it to the police then
then you wouldn't be able to
provide my husband with high-quality treatment
if you turn back time
would you have done something differently
I definitely wouldn't
I'm sorry
I was angry with you
that you are hiding everything but yourself
hardly said anything
so I don't say
no one listened to me
after all
I started hiding everything
the pain inside
even now I don't understand where to start
once upon a time
have a good evening good luck
and the small one has already been discharged
sent her to rest well done
good job
bye bye
good service
be careful
so as not to end up like me
I
I thought I'd figure it out later
but I was so consumed by the desire for revenge
that I didn’t notice how I pushed you away
I think
in this we are similar
thank you
you protected my 7
I left the goods in my personal safe
you should have it
from now on
we will trust each other completely
hwang dong hyun killed chan haegu
the matter will not be limited to sending Suavs to a juvenile colony
as soon as he is suspected
he'll dump everything
at you or at me
he will never let us go
what to do
let's get rid of chant haegu
let's get rid of him
so as not to tease
What does a guy have to change us?
money
have connections in China
don't worry everything will be fine
great hi guys
for money he will transport anyone anywhere and also
he can
kill
you will need
just invite him
others will do the rest for us, drag it
grab it heavy
come on
get in
and then
he won't come back
never
yes
and we'll sit here today
he said to wait here
he felt stuffy you see
let's have a quick bite, come on
dear
where was
you're barefoot
walked home like this
then gin
but I didn’t want to believe him
I kept hoping that he made you do it
against your will
no it's not like that
I can explain it to you
it's still not enough so you continue
none of this matters
there are things you can't do
can you even imagine
what happened to jenha's mom because of you
or you don't care
that others are dying
that's what you are and you don't care
that your family will die
that as long as others feel good, they don’t care if we die
sua yes
that's not what I meant
while you were dragging everything out of the house for the benefit of others
I spent every won I earned
working as a delivery driver for 15 years
it wasn't you who was the angel
that I worked for the sake of my family
it was me
and after all this
you blame me
seriously
don't you dare behave like that
it all started because of you
and it's true
it's all because of me
from everything the teacher said
I least wanted to believe it
dear I'm not
number hidden
dear
as soon as it's all over
it will be like it was
wait a little
if you can't stop
I'll do it, at least I'll try
wait what do you have
don't you dare
don't do this
number hidden
skoro vse zakonchitsya pravda pravda
사장님 도진
I hate waiting
I didn’t want my husband to know I brought it
that's all there is
전소
now the subscriber cannot
damn
this is the discount you gave
conhelimu
oh well
I returned everything
there eva
we're leaving we're leaving
I told you
nothing can be hidden from me
let's live together
unless you want to substitute 7 of course
you think they were just watching you
everything is fine
forgive me
I got diarrhea and not constipation
for money he will transport anyone
and anywhere as well
he can
kill
all you need is
invite him
and others will do the rest for us
I'll give you more
forget about them and listen to me
Most of all in life I don’t trust junkies
today
during an undercover transaction
trying to catch you
I was attacked
this is self-defense
Why would you listen to me and stay alive?
I'm so tired of hanging out with you
헤이
엔쓰u
damn it's a leech
on thin ice
let's run away
I don't want to run away
so that I can live on money
exchanged for you
wow what a beauty
you lost again you fool
teacher
maybe not like you said
taking advantage of other people's weaknesses
you're getting weaker
misfortune will look for you
what I hate most is injustice
translated and voiced by mobile studio
television ordered by online cinema ivi in 2025